#### Contact

contact.vipulelawadhi@gmail .com

www.linkedin.com/in/vipulelawadhi (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Statistical Modeling

**SQL** 

SAS

## Languages

English (Full Professional)

Hindi (Native or Bilingual)

German (Limited Working)

### Certifications

Tableau Analyst

Tableau Data Scientist

SAS Certified Base Programmer for SAS 9

AMCAT Certified Software Development Trainee

AMCAT Certified Data Processing Specialist

# Vipul Elawadhi

Senior Risk Analyst at NatWest(RBS)
Delhi

# Summary

Senior Risk Analyst at RBS with total 4.8 years' experience, interacting with Tech and Reporting Team for Requirement analysis. My core competencies include Strategy Thinking, Credit Risk knowledge, SQL, SAS, Shell scripting, Informatica (ETL), Control-M Job scheduler, Tableau, Qlikview and SAS VA for Dashboards.

## Experience

NatWest

Senior Risk Analyst September 2019 - Present (1 year)

Gurgaon, India

### CenturyLink

Software Engineer

July 2017 - September 2019 (2 years 3 months)

Noida Area, India

#### Aon

Analyst

November 2015 - July 2017 (1 year 9 months)

Noida Area, India

## Education

Indira Gandhi National Open University

Post Graduate Diploma in Applied Statistics, Mathematical Statistics and Probability · (2018 - 2019)

Delhi Institute Of Technology & Management

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Computer Science · (2011 - 2015)

Kulachi Hansraj Model School

High school, Science · (1996 - 2011)